Contact

307, 3rd Floor, Maplewood Apartment, OMR, Kazhipattur, Chennai - 603103. Landmark: Opp to Shell petrol punk 9585641065 (Mobile) ramaneee@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/raman-chidambaram-12329650 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Documaker

Tableau

Machine Learning

Languages

Tamil (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Udemy Certified - Tableau 2020 A-Z: Hands-on Tableau training for Data Science

Oracle Documaker Standard Edition 12 Implementation Essentials

Professional Scrum Master

RAMAN CHIDAMBARAM

CCM Consultant | Tableau Enthusiast | Professional Scrum Master | Aspiring Data Scientist

Chennai

Summary

10+ years of experience in Customer Communication Management & Content Management - involved in Analysis, Designing, Development, Testing, Implementation, Configuration, Maintenance, Production Support and Project Management.

Experienced and versatile solution architect, technical Leader, with a great combination of analytical, technical and resource-management skills in a wide variety of business applications.

Working as CCM Practitioner & Technical Architect in TCS, Chennai.

Specialties: Document Composition:-

- Oracle Documaker (All versions)
- Open text Exstream (HP Exstream)
- CCM Migration Framework design

Other Technologies:-

- Tableau Public/Desktop
- Devops, Agile scrum methodologies
- Python | Machine Learning | Deep Learning
- Windows/unix servers

Open to any technologies. Flexible to learn and explore it quickly.

Experience

Tata Consultancy Services
Technical Architect
May 2015 - Present (5 years 10 months)
Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Capgemini - Chennai Associate Consultant

September 2012 - May 2015 (2 years 9 months)

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Cognizant Technology Solutions - Coimbatore Programmer Analyst

December 2009 - August 2012 (2 years 9 months)

Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India

Education

I.R.T.T, Erode.

Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (2005 - 2009)

HSC : ITO Higher Secondary School Palani

· (2004 - 2005)

SSLC: ITO Higher Secondary School Palani

· (2001 - 2002)